

Kamil Koziół

Developer

Warsaw

kamkoziol1@gmail.com +48 660 592 116

https://kamilkoziol.github.io/portfolio

Profile

Young, energetic developer. Used to work in core banking systems however eventually got fed up with huge, inflexible, 30 years old systems with enormous technical debt. Looking for something new and fresh to get excited about. Especially interested in neural networks and machine learning solutions in general.

Employment History

Sep 2017 — Jan 2022

Warsaw

T24/Java Developer at Deloitte Consulting SA

- · Core Banking system implementation,
- Solution architect responsible for design, implementation and delivery of T24 integration services,
- Integration with external systems using Apache Camel to create and orchestrate REST APIs,
- · Integration with external systems using JMS queues,
- Developing banking logic and functional solutions in Java and JBasic,

Jan 2017 — Dec 2018

Warsaw

Mathematics and physics tutor at Foster High

- Preparing high school students for final exams and International Baccalaureate,
- Leading and guiding students in the course of their education process,
- · Specialized in calculus, arithmetic and algebra,
- · Work in both English and Polish

Education

Mar 2018 — Jul 2022

Warsaw University of Technology

Warsaw

Master's degree

- · in progress
- Building system to scan and recognize facial features in order to determine scanned person age, ethnicity and gender based on deep learning artificial neural networks
- Researching different approaches and different neural network architectures to archive best possible age estimation

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Skills

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

React

Python

TensorFlow / ML

Flask

Pandas/Sklearn

Docker/Kubernetes/AWS

• • • • • • • •

Git

Jenkins

Languages

English

Polish

Hobbies

New technologies, chess, 20 years old computer games

Bachelor's degree

- Focused on elaborating steering algorithm for autonomous cars basing on Neural Networks and Genetic Algorithms
- Required implementing of realistic car models, developing and teaching MLP network in order to provide user-pleasant model of car steering

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).